[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following actors did not appear in the 1996 film Trees Lounge?", "correct_answer": "Mark Ruffalo", "incorrect_answers": ["Steve Buscemi", "Rockets Redglare", "Elizabeth Bracco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Thomas Harris created this terrible fictional murderer.", "correct_answer": "Hannibal Lecter", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael  Everett", "Garland  Saunderson", "Jason Thomas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the Latin terms that refer to plant and animal life?", "correct_answer": "flora and fauna", "incorrect_answers": ["etcetera and et alia", "habeas and corpus", "ipso and facto"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Given the equation C=pi*D. What does the C and the D stand for?", "correct_answer": "The circumference and diameter of a circle", "incorrect_answers": ["The electrical capacitance and the electrical dipole", "The circular radius and the diopter distance", "The cranial area and the circumspectum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the mansion in the 1940 movie Rebecca?", "correct_answer": "Manderly", "incorrect_answers": ["Mandaly", "Manchester", "Morgan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Approximately how fast can a sneeze travel?", "correct_answer": "100 miles per hour", "incorrect_answers": ["500 miles an hour", "100 feet per hour", "50 feet an hour"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which is the force that binds together protons and neutrons together and thus forms the atoms nucleus?", "correct_answer": "Strong interaction", "incorrect_answers": ["Electromagnetic force", "Gravitation", "Weak interaction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The correct way to measure the size of a widescreen monitor or laptop display is by length of the longer side.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Bruce Willis character in the 1988 movie Die Hard?", "correct_answer": "John McClane", "incorrect_answers": ["Harry Ellis", "Richard Thornburg", "Al Powell"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which form of cancer is the number one cause of cancer deaths in both men and women in the United States?", "correct_answer": "Lung Cancer", "incorrect_answers": ["Prostate Cancer", "Breast Cancer", "Leukemia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1999 movie was written and directed by M. Night Shyamalan.", "correct_answer": "The Sixth Sense", "incorrect_answers": ["Signs", "American Beauty", "Unbreakable"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where is the International Tennis Hall of Fame located?", "correct_answer": "Newport, Rhode Island", "incorrect_answers": ["London, England", "New York, NY", "Paris, France"]}]